Guide to the Arthur Levitt, Jr. Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series XIII: SEC Correspondents Index
  - Beresford, Dennis R. Financial Accounting Standards Board; University of Georgia - J.M. Tull School of Accounting, FROM: Jan. 6, 1995; Mar. 9, 1995; Jul. 31, 1995; Apr. 5, 1996; May 19, 1997; Apr. 6, 1998; TO: Jan. 19, 1995; Mar. 16 1995; Aug. 29, 1995; Dec. [5], 1995; Apr. 24, 1996; Apr. 15, 1998
  - Berg, David, FROM: Dec. 8, 1994
  - Berger, David, Esq. Berger & Montague, P.C. FROM: Jul. 29, 1993; TO: Aug. 4, 1993
  - Berko, Malcolm Trading Stock, FROM: Jun. 14, 1995; TO: Jun. 28, 1995
  - Berkson, Edward J. Locust Street Securities, Inc. FROM: Dec. 1, 1997; TO: Mar. 4, 1998
  - Berlanda, Enzo Comissione Nazionale per le Societa e la Borsa, Italy, FROM: Aug. 11, 1993; Feb. 2, 1996; TO: Aug. 18, 1993; Feb. 6, 1996; Feb. 27, 1996; Dec. 26, 1996
  - Berman, Howard L. US House of Representatives, FROM: Oct. 10, 1996; Dec. 10, 1997; TO: Dec. 10, 1996; Jan. 20, 1998
  - Berman, Norman New York University Leonard N. Stern School of Business, TO: May 2, 1995
  - Berry, Joanah US SEC - Office of Investor Education, TO: Dec. 3, 1998
  - Bertera, William J. American Public Works Association, TO: Jan. 9, 1997
  - Berthel, Thomas J. Berthel Fisher & Co Financial Services Inc. FROM: Apr. 21, 1997; TO: May 22, 1997
  - Bertram, Janine, TO: Aug. 14, 1997
  - Beyer, John T. PFS Investments, Inc. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Bialkin, Kenneth J. Skadden, Arps, Slate, Meagher & Flom, TO: Oct. 23, 1995; Mar. 6, 1996; May 7, 1996; Mar. 5, 1998
  - Bibliowicz, Jessica Smith Barney; John A. Levin & Co.; TO: Mar. 8, 1995; Mar. 16, 1999
  - Biggins, J. Veronica Heidrick & Struggles, FROM: [Jul.], 1997; TO: Jul. 23, 1997
  - Biggs, John H. TIAA-CREF, FROM: Jul. 15, 1999; TO: Nov. 6, 1996; Aug. 16, 1999; Nov. 27, 2000
  - Bilbray, Brian P. US House of Representatives, TO: Feb. 18, 1997
  - Billici, George W. Cravath, Swaine & Moore, TO: Dec. 23, 1996
  - Bindenagel, J.D. US Embassy, Germany, FROM: May 21, 1997; TO: Apr. 25, 1997; Jul. 16, 1997
  - Binder, Gordon M. Amgen, Inc. TO: May 1, 1995
  - Birnbaum, Robert J. FROM:Jun. 21, 1999; TO: Jul. 21, 1999
  - Bishop, Keith Paul Department of Corporations, CA, FROM: Nov. 13, 1996 (See also Griffin, Mark, Jan. 27, 1997); TO: Jan. 17, 1997
  - Bishop, William G. Institute of Internal Auditors, FROM: Jun. 6, 1997; TO: Jun. 27, 1997; Jun. 13, 1999
  - Bingaman, Jeff US Senate, FROM: Apr. 21, 1999; TO: Jun. 14, 1999
  - Birgfeld, Frank J. National Association of Securities Dealers Regulation, Inc. TO: May 14, 1998
  - Black, Ella M. US SEC - Office of Municipal Securities, TO: Feb. 5, 1996
  - Blackmore, Robert L. FROM: Apr. 30, 1998; TO: May 11, 1998
  - Blair, Shila, C. Commodity Futures Trading Commission, FROM: Jul. 30, 1993; TO: Aug. 4, 1993
  - Blair, Warren E. US SEC - Chief Administrative Law Judge, FROM: Feb. 28, 1994
  - Blandin, Don American Savings Education Council, TO: Apr. 14, 1998; May 22, 2000
  - Blant, Roy US House of Representatives, FROM: Sep. 27, 2000; TO: Oct. 31, 2000
  - Blaydon, Colin C. Dartmouth College, TO: Apr. 26, 1995
  - Blea, Arthur Pojoaque Valley Schools, TO: Jun. 19, 1996 (RE: John Rivera-Dirks)
  - Blezarde, Thomas Williams Alumni Review, TO: Aug. 27, 1998
  - Bliley, Thomas J. US House of Representatives, FROM: Mar. 3, 1996; Mar. 5, 1996; Apr. 23, 1996; Feb. 5, 1997; May 2, 1997; May 23, 1997 (filed under Buffet, Warren, Aug. 25, 1997); Jun. 16, 1997; Apr. 24, 1998; Nov. 18, 1998; Jan. 20, 2000; Apr. 3, 2000; May 8, 2000; Jun. 20, 2000; Jul. 13, 2000; T
  - Block, Dennis J. Cadwalader, Wickersham & Taft, TO: May 30, 2000
  - Bluestain, Sanfurd G. FROM: Oct. [21], 1997; Sep. [20], 1999; TO: Aug. 6, 1993; Oct. 30, 1997; Oct. 12, 1999
  - Blum, Andrew M. C.E. Unterberg, Towbin International, FROM: Jun. 8, 2000; TO: Jun. 14, 2000
  - Blumenthal, Richard Attorney General, CT, FROM: Sep. 21, 2000; TO: Oct. 31, 2000; Nov. 27, 2000
  - Blunt, Roy US House of Representatives, FROM: Jul. 9, 1997; Sep. 27, 2000; TO: Aug. 1, 1997; Nov. 14, 1997; Oct. 31, 2000
  - Boaz, Thomas M. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Boehmler, Sarah Porter, FROM: Feb. 5, 1997; TO: Feb. 14, 1997
  - Boehner, John A. US House of Representatives, FROM: Feb. 2, 1999; TO: Feb. 23, 1999
  - Boggs, Lindy Tulane University, TO: May 2, 1996
  - Bogle, John C. (Jack) Vanguard Group, FROM: May 19, 1998; Feb. 22, 1999; TO: Apr. 26, 1995; Jun. 19, 1998; Dec. 1, 1998; Mar. 5, 1999; Mar. 31, 1999; Nov. 27, 2000
  - Bohan, Gloria Omega World Travel, TO: Mar. 18, 1997 (RE: Downs, Phil); Oct. 28, 1997
  - Bollinger, Debra M. Division of Securities, SD (Director), TO: Apr. 21, 1995
  - Bon, Helene Federation des Experts Comptables Europeens, Belguim, FROM: Jan. 24, 2000; TO: Mar. 27, 2000
  - Bond, Christopher S. US Senate, TO: Apr. 7, 1997; Mar. 31, 1999
  - Bonilla, Henry US House of Representatives, TO: Mar. 27, 1995
  - Bonior, David E. US House of Representatives, FROM: Oct. 10, 1996; TO: Dec. 10, 1996
  - Booker, Walter K. Sponsors for Educational Opportunity, FROM: Feb. 9, 1998; TO: Mar. 18, 1998
  - Bookey, Jack H. US SEC - Seattle Office, FROM: Jul. 29, 1993; TO: Aug. 4, 1993
  - Booren, Steve Smith Barney Shearson, Inc, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Boosalis, Helen American Association of Retired Persons, TO: Apr. 20, 1995; May 2, 1996
  - Borchers, Eric S. Boy Scouts of America, TO: Jul. 17, 1998
  - Borders, Brian T. Association of Publicly Traded Companies, FROM: Feb. 23, 1995; TO: Feb. 24, 1995
  - Borg, Joseph Securities Commission, CA, TO: Apr. 21, 1995; Oct. 25, 1995 (+list)
  - Boris, James R. Kemper Securities, Inc. TO: Mar. 2, 1995; Apr. 20, 1995; Jun. 7, 1995
  - Born, Brooksley Commodity Futures Trading Commission, FROM: Dec. 9, 1996; Jan. 7, 1997; Jan. 28, 1997; Feb. 5, 1997; Feb. 10, 1997; Feb. 14, 1997; TO: Dec. 26, 1996; Jan. 17, 1997; Feb. 7, 1997; Feb. 14, 1997
  - Bortner, Deborah Securities Division, WA, TO: Apr. 21, 1995
  - Bosley, Daniel US House of Representatives, TO: May 9, 1995
  - Bothwell, James L. US Government Accounting Office, FROM: Sep. 26, 1995 (filed under Hatfield, Nov. 15, 1995)
  - Boucher, John US SEC, TO: Sep. 29, 1995
  - Bowden, William P. Societe Generale USA, FROM: Mar. 7, 1997; TO: Apr. 4, 1997
  - Bowlding, Michael US SEC - Print Shop, TO: Oct. 6, 1997
  - Bowles, Erskine B. White House - Deputy Chief of Staff; Forstmann Little & Co. FROM: Dec. 18, 1996; TO: Jun. 12, 1995; Dec. 4, 1996; Dec. 10, 1997; Jan. 29, 2001
  - Bowman, Thomas A. Association for Investment Management and Research, FROM: Dec. 14, 1994; TO: Jan. 11, 1995
  - Bowsher, Charles A. US Comptroller General; Public Oversight Board; FROM: Jun. 27, 1996; Dec. 9, 1999 (Turner, Lynn); TO: Aug. 22, 1996; Aug. 26, 1996; May 27, 1997(Balamaci, N.); Dec. 21, 1999 (Turner, Lynn)
  - Box, Michael House of Representatives, AL, FROM: Mar. 18, 1997; TO: Mar. 26, 1997
  - Boxer, Barbara US Senate, FROM: Jan. 23, 1995; TO: Feb. 6, 1995; Feb. 7, 1995
  - Boyce, Ralph US Embassy, Thailand, TO: May 5, 1995
  - Boyles, Harlan E. Treasurer, NC, FROM: Feb. 4, 1994 (Clinton, William); Nov. 3, 1995; TO: Nov. 27, 1995
  - Breeden, Richard C. Coopers & Lybrand; Richard C. Breeden & Co. TO: Aug. 6, 1993; Jul. 7, 1995; Oct. 5, 1995; Apr. 15, 1996; Nov. 5, 1996; Nov. 6, 1996; Jul. 28, 2000
  - Brennan, John J. Vanguard Group, FROM: May 9, 1996; Apr. 7, 1998; TO: Jun. 5, 1996; Apr. 23, 1998; Oct. 13, 2000; Jan. 29, 2001
  - Brennan, John C. Vanguard Group, TO: Apr. 17, 1998
  - Brennan, Ursula, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Brademas, John New York University - President Emeritus, FROM: Apr. 23, 1999; TO: May 18, 1999
  - Bradford, J.C. J.C. Bradford & Co. TO: Aug. 23, 1995
  - Bradley, Harold S. American Century, TO: Oct. 15, 1999
  - Brady, M. Jane Office of Attorney General, DE, FROM: Sep. 25, 1997; TO: Oct. 16, 1997
  - Brakatselos, George Bond Market Trade Association - Municipal Securities Division, TO: Jan. 9, 1997
  - Braun, David B. US SEC, TO: May 7, 1996
  - Bredesen, Philip Mayor, Nashville, TN, TO: Aug. 21 1995
  - Breuer, Rolf Deutsche Bank AG, Germany, TO: Dec. 24, 1998
  - Breyer, Stephen G. US Supreme Court, TO: Oct. 5, 1998
  - Brickman, Mark US SEC - Web Development, TO: Sep. 29, 1995
  - Bridger, Jeffrey DLS Group, Inc. TO: Feb. 17, 1995
  - Brill, Jesse M. Corporate Counsel, FROM: Mar. 7, 1996; TO: Mar. 22, 1996
  - Brinkley, James W. Legg Mason Wood Walker, Inc. FROM: Jul. 27, 2000; TO: Aug. 15, 2000
  - Brittan, Leon UBS Warburg, UK, TO: Jan. 29, 2001
  - Broadnax, Walter D. American University - School of Public Affairs, FROM: Aug. 16, 2000; TO: Nov. 2, 2000
  - Brodkin, A. Keith Massachusetts Financial Services, FROM: Jul. 3, 1997; TO: Aug. 26, 1997
  - Brodsky, William J. Chicago Mercantile Exchange; Chicago Board Options Exchange, FROM: Aug. 6, 1993; May 3, 1995; Jun. 21, 1995; Nov. 10, 1995; Mar. 20, 1998; Sep. 28, 1999; Oct. 7, 1999; Dec. 6, 1999; Jul. 31, 2000; TO: Aug. 23, 1993; May 22, 1995; Jul. 17, 1995; Sep. 13, 1995; Nov. 30, 1995; Jul. 29, 1997; Jan. 28, 1998; May 8, 199
  - Brody, Christopher W. E.M. Warburg, Pincus & Co., Inc. FROM: Jul. 17, 1996; TO: Jul. 31, 1996
  - Bromark, Raymond, TO: May 11, 1998
  - Bronstein, Louis, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Brooks, E. R. Central and South West Corp. TO: Dec. 5, 1997
  - Brooks, Russell J. Market Profile Theorems, Inc. FROM: Mar. 29, 1995; TO: Apr. 18, 1995
  - Brophy, Mary Alice Dain Bosworth Inc. TO: Feb. 17, 1995
  - Brophy, Raymond C. Judiciary Plaza Limited Partnership, FROM: Apr. 13, 1998; TO: Apr. 15, 1998
  - Brotbaker, Teri A. US SEC - Northeast Regional Office, TO: Feb. 24, 1995
  - Brown, David A. Ontario Securities Commission, Canada, TO: Mar. 3, 1999; Nov. 27, 2000
  - Brown, George E., Jr. US House of Representatives, FROM: Oct. 10, 1996; Dec. 10, 1997; TO: Dec. 10, 1996; Jan. 20, 1998
  - Brown, Janet H. Commission on Presidential Debates, FROM: Jan. 25, 2001; TO: Jan. 29, 2001
  - Brown, John W. Stryker Corporation, FROM: Sep. 3, 1996
  - Brown, Ronald H. US Department of Commerce, TO: Mar. [14], 1995
  - Brown, Sherrod US House of Representatives, FROM: Oct. 10, 1996; TO: Dec. 10, 1996
  - Brown, Stephen L. John Hancock Mutual Life Insurance Company, FROM: Apr. 3, 1996; TO: Mar. 2, 1995; Apr. 20, 1995; May 1, 1995; Apr. 30, 1996
  - Brownback, Sam US Senate, TO: Nov. 20, 1997
  - Brubaker, Matthew S. Boy Scouts of America, TO: Jul. 17, 1998
  - Brundisi, Geraldine M. TO: Aug. 12, 1993
  - Bruns, Hans-Georg Daumier-Benz AG, FROM: Nov. 15, 1995; Jan. 11, 1996; TO: Jan. 2, 1996; Feb. 5, 1996
  - Bryan, John H. Sara Lee Corporation, FROM: Feb. 4, 2000; TO: Feb. 9, 2000
  - Bryan, Richard US Senate, FROM: Apr. 21, 1995; TO: May 11, 1995; Mar. 5, 1999
  - Bryant, John US House of Representatives, TO: Mar. 27, 1995
  - Bryant, Keith, Jr. Institute of Management Accountants, FROM: Mar. 25, 1998; TO: Apr. 16, 1998
  - Buchalter, Stuart D. Buchalter, Nemer, Fields & Younger, FROM: Jan. 29, 1996; TO: Feb. 16, 1996
  - Buckham, Rod The PatriotMini Storage, Inc. FROM: [Apr. 10], 1998; TO: Apr. 27, 1998
  - Budge, Hamer H. FROM: Feb. 22, 1999; TO: Oct. 5, 1995; Nov. 5, 1996 (filed under Oct. 28, 1997); Oct. 28, 1997; Mar. 9, 1999
  - Buesinger, Ronald E. A.G. Edwards & Sons, Inc. TO: Feb. 17, 1995; Apr. 26, 1995
  - Buffett, Warren E. Bershire Hathaway, Inc. FROM: Aug. 21, 1995; Mar. 29, 1999; Aug. 7, 2000; Oct. 31, 2000; TO: May 1, 1995; Sep. 13, 1995; Feb. 10, 1997; Aug. 25, 1997; Jun. 23, 1998; Apr. 5, 1999; Apr. 12, 1999; Aug. 21, 2000
  - Bumpers, Dale US Senate, FROM: Jul. 14, 1993 (Mary Shapiro); TO: Aug. 3, 1993
  - Burdick, Brad Internet Multicasting Service, TO: Oct. 10, 1995
  - Burnett, Robert US SEC - Division of Corporation Finance, TO: Oct. 11, 1995
  - Burnham, Christopher B. Treasurer, CT. FROM: Aug. 21, 1995; TO: Sep. 21, 1995
  - Burnham, I. W. Burnham Asset Management Corp. FROM: Oct. 9, 1995; TO: Oct. 25, 1995
  - Burnham, I. W., II Burnham Securities, Inc. FROM: May 31, 1996; Aug. 11, 1999; TO: Jun. 13, 1996; Sep. 2, 1999
  - Burson, Charles Office of Vice-President, USA, TO: Apr. 29, 1998
  - Burstein, Daniel Blackstone Group, TO: Mar. 26, 1996
  - Burton, Dan US House of Representatives, TO: Mar. 13, 1998; Jul. 20, 1998; Jan. 4, 1999; Mar. 3, 2000; Aug. 22, 2000
  - Busch, Cheryl Charlie National Association of Securities Dealers, TO: Feb. 17 1995; Aug. 24, 1995
  - Bush, George H. President, USA, TO: Nov. 24, 1998
  - Butler, Jonathan US SEC - Operations, TO: Sep. 29, 1995
  - Butler, Saumel C. Cravath, Swaine & Moore, TO: Feb. 27, 1998
  - Butler, Stephen KPMG, LLP, TO: Oct. 3, 2000; Nov. 27, 2000; Jan. 29, 2001; Jan. 29, 2001
  - Butowsky, David M. Gordon Altman Butowsky Weitzen Shalov & Wein, TO: Mar. 16, 1999
  - Byerly, Thomas J. Franklin Financial Services Corporation, TO: Mar. 2, 1995; Apr. 20, 1995
  - Byrne, Leslie L. White House - Special Assistant to the President, FROM: Mar. 26, 1997; TO: Apr. 21, 1997
  - Burnes, Nanette Business Week, TO: Apr. 15, 1999
  - Caccese, Michael S. Association for Investment Management and Research, FROM: Oct. 27, 1995; Nov. 13, 1995; May 13, 1996; Oct. 7, 1996; Mar. 26, 1997; TO: Oct. 3, 1995; Nov. 8, 1995; Nov. 27, 1995; Mar. 6, 1996; Jul. 18, 1996; Oct. 29, 1996; Apr. 23, 1997
  - Cacheris, Elaine M. US SEC - Pacific Regional Office, TO: Feb. 27, 1995; Dec. 30, 1996
  - Cadigan, Patrick F. Gateway Communications, Inc. FROM: Aug. 5, 1993; TO: Aug. 25, 1993
  - Cafardi, Nicholas P. Duquesne University School of Law, TO: Dec. 20, 2000
  - Cafferty, Thomas D. Cafferty-Commercial Real Estate Service, FROM: Apr. 6, 1998; TO: Apr. 15, 1998
  - Calahan, Walter P. Walter P. Calahan Photography, Inc. FROM: Dec. 13, 2000 (Ullman, Chris); TO: Dec. 19, 2000
  - Caldwell, Jacqueline H. FROM: Sep. 15, 1995; TO: Sep. 22, 1995
  - Calello, Paul CSFP Capital, Inc. TO: Apr. 10, 1997
  - Calfas, John A. FROM: Aug. 24, 1993: TO: Sep. 13, 1993
  - Callaway, Howard Callaway Gardens, FROM: Mar. 20, 1997 (Filed under Scardino, Jennifer, Apr. 6, 1997)
  - Cameron, Alan Australian Securities and Investment Commission, Australia, FROM: Dec. 2, 1996; Sep. 28, 1998; TO: May 28, 1996; Dec. 26, 1996; Jan. 22, 1997; Nov. 18, 1997; Oct. 26, 1998; Nov. 19, 1998; Mar. 3, 1999
  - Cameron, Edward L. PriceWaterhouseCoopers, LLP, TO: Mar. 16, 1999
  - Campbell, Robert H. Sun Company, Inc (Sunoco), FROM: Mar. 26, 1998; TO: Apr. 14, 1998
  - Campbell, Tom US House of Representatives, FROM: May 20, 1996; TO: Jun. 13, 1996; Nov. 18, 1997
  - Canaday, Lemuel US SEC, TO: Sep. 29, 1995
  - Canadell, Eudald International Organization of Securities Commissions, Canada; MEFF Renta, Spain, FROM: Jul. 8, 1997; Feb. 15, 1999; TO: Feb. 1995; Apr. 5, 1996; Aug. 12, 1997; Aug. 13, 1997; Jul. 23, 1998; Mar. 17, 1999
  - Canady, Lemuel L. US SEC - Desktop Publishing, TO: Oct. 6, 1997
  - Candela, Stephen L. US SEC - Philadelphia Office, TO: Sep. 8, 2000
  - Cannata, Salvator Department of Banking, CT - Division of Securities, TO: Feb. 17 1995
  - Canseco, Leo Certified Financial Planner Board of Standards, TO: May 14, 1998
  - Capillo, Felisa, FROM: Mar. 8, 1996; TO: Mar. 13, 1996
  - Capone, Richard Warburg Dillion Read, TO: Jan. 5, 1999
  - Cardinali, Joseph L. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Cardozo, Michael A. Association of the Bar of the City of New York, TO: Dec. 31, 1996; Aug. 29, 1997
  - Carey, Gordon Towers Perrin, TO: May 1, 1995
  - Carey, Paul White House, FROM: Dec. 10, 1996
  - Carlson, James B. Mayer, Brown & Platt, FROM: Dec. 31, 1997; TO: Jan. 21, 1998
  - Carlson, JoEllen New York Stock Exchange, TO: Feb. 17 1995
  - Carlson, Tim Boy Scouts of America, FROM: Feb. 10, 1998 (filed under Mar. 24, 1998)
  - Carlucci, Frank C. Carlyle Group, TO: May 31, 1995; Jun. 7, 1995; Apr. 22, 1999; Jan. 29, 2001
  - Carman, Gregory W. US Court of International Trade, TO: Jul. 19, 1998
  - Carmichael, Douglas R. CUNY - Baruch College, TO: Nov. 27, 2000
  - Carney, William J. Emory University, FROM: Jul. 2, 1993; TO: Aug. 16, 1993
  - Carpenter, Edmund M. General Signal Corporation, TO: May 1, 1995
  - Carpenter, Keith US SEC, TO: May 3, 1995
  - Carpenter, Michael A. Salomon Smith Barney Holdings, Inc. TO: Nov. 23, 1998; Aug. 4, 1999
  - Carroll, Lawrence P. Alaska Division of Banking, Securities and Corporation, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Carroll, Thomas J. Prudential Insurance Company of America, FROM: Oct. 21, 1999; TO: Nov. 22, 1999
  - Carson, Julia US House of Representatives, FROM: Nov. 20, 1997; Nov. 20, 1997; May 9, 2000; TO: Jan. 20, 1998 (2); Jun. 20, 2000
  - Carswell, Robert Shearman & Sterling, TO: Nov. 6, 1996
  - Carter, Marshall N. State Street Bank & Trust Co. TO: Dec. 2, 1998
  - Case, Steve America Online, TO: Dec. 23, 1998
  - Cassidy, J. B. North American Securities Administrators Association, Inc. - Investment Companies Sales Practice Committee, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Castillo, Eugenio, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Castine, Michael P. Highland Search Group, LLC, FROM: Feb. 4, 1997; TO: Feb. [12], 1997
  - Castle, John K. Castle Harlan, Inc. FROM: Dec. 16, 1997; Nov. 11, 1998; Dec. 8, 1998; TO: Mar. 28, 1996; Dec. 19, 1996; Jan. [5], 1998; Nov. 18, 1998; Dec. 21, 1998
  - Catell, Robert B. Brooklyn Union, FROM: Aug. 1, 1995
  - Catlett, Jason Junkbusters, Inc. FROM: May 9, 2000; TO: Jun. 20, 2000
  - Caughey, Robert M. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Cavahagh, Richard E. Conference Board, FROM: Oct. 13, 1997; TO: Oct. 30, 1997; Jan. 29, 2001
  - Cavicke, David US House of Representatives, TO: Mar. 5, 1997
  - Cayne, James E. Bear, Stearns & Co, Inc. FROM: Aug. 14, 1995; Apr. 22, 1996; Mar. 3, 1997; Jun. 2, 1999; TO: Mar. 2, 1995; Mar. 27, 1995; Apr. 20, 1995; Jun. 7, 1995; May 8, 1996; Jan. 30. 1997; Mar. 21, 1997; Apr. 10, 1997; Oct. 17, 1997; Oct. 23, 1997; Apr. 8, 1998; Oct. 22, 1998; Nov. 23, 1
  - Cella, Eugene Office of the Secretary of State, NC, TO: Apr. 21, 1995
  - Cha, Laura Securities and Futures Commission, Hong Kong, TO: Aug. 9, 2000
  - Chabot, Steve US House of Representatives, FROM: May 4, 1998; TO: May 11, 1998
  - Chadbourne, Sally US House of Representatives, TO: Dec. 11, 1995
  - Chafee, John H. US Senate, FROM: Feb. 1, 1995TO: Feb. 13, 1995
  - Chalmers, Geoffrey T. Commonwealth Equity Services, Inc. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Chalsty, John S. Donaldson, Lufkin & Jenrette Securities Corp. TO: Mar 2, 1995; Mar. 27, 1995; Apr. 20, 1995; Jun. 7, 1995; Aug. 15, 1997; Oct. 23, 1997; Apr. 8, 1998; Jan. 29, 2001
  - Chamberlain, Wendy US Embassy, Malaysia, FROM: Apr. 27, 1995 (See Carlucci, May. 31); TO: May 5, 1995; May 12, 1995
  - Chan-Fishel, Michelle Friends of the Earth, TO: Apr. 14, 1998
  - Chapman, Alger B. Chicago Board Options Exchange, FROM: Nov. 15, 1995; Feb. 5, 1997; TO: Jan. 12, 1995; Feb. 17, 1995; Jul. 7, 1995; Sep. 13, 1995; Dec. 7, 1995; Feb. 14, 1997
  - Chapman, Craig Brown and Wood, Japan, FROM: Feb. 9, 1995; Jun. 6, 1995; TO: Feb. 27, 1995; Jun. 20, 1995
  - Chapman, Debra US SEC - Procurement, TO: Sep. 29, 1995
  - Chapman, Jim US House of Representatives, TO: Mar. 27, 1995
  - Charles, Jim Charles Schwab & Co, Inc. TO: Feb. 17 1995
  - Chaves, Fred L. US SEC - Central Regional Office, TO: May 14, 1998
  - Cheney, Richard B. Vice President Elect, USA, TO: [n.d.] (fragment)
  - Chernow, Ron Wall Street Journal, TO: Nov. 12, 1999
  - Childers, Frank Securities Division, WV, TO: Apr. 21, 1995
  - Chorba, Timothy A. US Embassy, Singapore - Ambassador, TO: May 5, 1995
  - Chretien, Raymond Ambassador to USA, Canada, FROM: Dec. 17, 1999; TO: Jan. 13, 2000
  - Christesen, Donald J. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Christopher, Warren US Department of State, TO: [Mar. 14], 1995; Nov. 5, 1996
  - Chubais, Anatoly B. Russian Federation on Securities and Stock Market, Moscow, Russia, FROM: May 18, 1995; Nov. 3, 1995; TO: Jun. 20, 1995; Nov. 27, 1995; Dec. 4, 1995
  - Churchill, Buntzie Ellis World Affairs Council of Philadelphia, FROM: Jan. 5, 1996; TO: Feb. 5, 1996
  - Cieplensky, Bette New York Stock Exchange, TO: Feb. 17 1995
  - Cinman, Andrew Jason MacKenzie Securities, Inc. FROM: Sep. 16, 1993: TO: Sep. 21, 1993
  - Clapp, David C. Goldman Sachs Group, L.P. FROM: Apr. 21, 1997; TO: Jun. 12, 1997
  - Clapp, Priscilla US Embassy, Republic of South Africa, TO: Mar. 7, 1995
  - Clark, Howard L. Lehman Brothers Holdings, Inc. FROM: Jul. 27, 2000; TO: Aug. 15, 2000
  - Clark, Peter International Organization of Securities Commissions, Canada, TO: Apr. 3, 2000
  - Clarke, Alvaro Superintendencia de Valores y Seguros, Chile, TO: Mar. 21, 2000
  - Clarke, Henry D. Clarke Ice Cream Co. TO: Dec. 19, 1996
  - Clarke, Robert L. Bracewell & Patterson, LLP, FROM: Feb. 18, 1999; TO: Apr. 1, 1999
  - Clarkson, James US SEC - Division of Enforcement, TO: May 14, 1998
  - Cleary, Kevin F. FROM: Apr. 2, 1998; TO: Apr. 27, 1998
  - Cleland, Max US Senate, FROM: Jun. 20, 1997; Oct. 22, 1997; TO: Jul. 21, 1997; Nov. 14, 1997; Feb. 12, 1998
  - Clement, Bob US House of Representatives, TO: Aug. 21 1995
  - Clifton, Lance A. US SEC - Northeast Regional Office, TO: Feb. 24, 1995
  - Clinger, William F., Jr. US House of Representatives, FROM: Feb. 6, 1996; Dec. 20, 1995; Jun. 17, 1996; TO: Feb. 17, 1995; Aug. 10, 1995; Nov. 15, 1995; Jan. 3, 1996; Feb. 9, 1996; Feb. 20, 1996; Jun. 3, 1996; Jul. 8, 1996; Oct. 2, 1996
  - Clinton, William J. President, USA, FROM: Apr. 1, 1994 (personal file); Jan. 5, 1995; Feb. 20, 1998; TO: Jan. 6, 1995; May 9, 1995; Jun. 16. 1995; Dec. 29, 1995; Feb. 9, 1996; Apr. 15, 1996 (fax of letter dated Dec. 19, 1995); Jun. 19, 1996; Jul. 21, 1997 (Owens, Helen); Dec. 22, 1997; May
  - Clurman, David Phillips, Nizer, Benjamin, Krim & Ballon, FROM: Apr. 13, 1995; TO: May 1, 1995; Oct. 16, 1998
  - Cloonan, James B. American Association of Individual Investors, TO: Apr. 20, 1995; May 2, 1996
  - Coates, Joseph M. US SEC - Print Shop, TO: Oct. 6, 1997
  - Coburn, Tom US House of Representatives, to: Dec. 4, 1995
  - Cochran, Martha American Bar Association, TO: May 14, 1998
  - Cochran, Thad US Senate, TO: Nov. 20, 1997; Nov. 24, 1998
  - Coelho, Tony, FROM: Feb. 23, 1995
  - Coffee, John C. Columbia University Law School, TO: Apr. 26, 1995; Mar. 16, 1999; Nov. 27, 2000
  - Cohen, Charles Creative BioMolecules, TO: May 1, 1995
  - Cohen, Saul S. Rosenman & Colin, FROM: Feb. 14, 1995; TO: Mar. 6, 1995
  - Cohen, Sheldon S. FROM: May 3, 1996
  - Cohen, Sylvan M. Drinker Biddle & Reath LLP; Pennsylvania Real Estate Investment Trust, FROM: Feb. 10, 1998; Jan. 4, 2000; TO: Feb. 13, 1998; [Jan. 5], 2000
  - Cohen, William S. US Senate, TO: Mar. 16, 1995
  - Cohn, Robert Octel Corporation, FROM: Apr. 16, 1997; TO: May 8, 1997
  - Coia, Arthur Laborers' International Union of North America, FROM: May 9, 1995; TO: May 31, 1995
  - Cole, Thomas A. Sidley & Austin, TO: Apr. 30, 1998
  - Coleman, John A. Boardroom Consultants, FROM: Mar. 26, 1999; TO: Apr. 13, 1999
  - Coleman, Ronald D. US House of Representatives, TO: Mar. 27, 1995
  - Coleman, William T. O'Melveny & Myers, TO: Nov. 18, 1997
  - Colker, David Cincinnati Stock Exchange, FROM: Jun. 10, 1998; TO: Oct. 25, 1995; Mar. 7, 1997; Jun. 30, 1998
  - Collins, Cardiss US House of Representatives, TO: Aug. 10, 1995
  - Collins, Susan M. US Senate, FROM: Jun. 20, 1997; Oct. 22, 1997; TO: Jul. 21, 1997; Nov. 14, 1997; Feb. 12, 1998; Mar. 26, 1999; Sep. 21, 1999 (2)
  - Colin, Justin S. Smith Barney Inc. FROM: May 20, 1999; TO: May [26-30], 1999
  - Colish, Faith Faith Colish, PC, TO: Mar. 16, 1999
  - Colodner, Michael Office of Court Administration, TO: Feb. 13, 1998
  - Colonna, Anthony New York Stock Exchange, TO: Feb. 17, 1995
  - Colson, Robert H. The CPA Jounal, FROM: Dec. 20, 2000
  - Colwell, Marcus Goldman Sachs & Co. TO: Dec. 23, 1996
  - Combest, Larry US House of Representatives, FROM: Jan. 20, 2000; TO: Mar. 2, 2000
  - Conaway, Michael State Board of Public Accountancy, TX, TO: Nov. 27, 2000